<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Diduknow]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Diduknow]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/diduknow/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 06:02:56 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/diduknow/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Report: Here's How Many People Fatally Overdosed On Marijuana In 2015]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Report: Here's How Many People Fatally Overdosed On Marijuana In 2015</h1><p>Marijuana legalization has been the talk of North America for years now. It's arguable that one of the biggest campaign promises made by Canada's new Prime Minister, Justin Trudeau, was his goal to legalize cannabis countrywide. In the US, cannabis is legal in some form in 23 states, and with that we see a staggering number we [...]</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/6e6a307f1c7cda7a8694b9c4bef0d07af70e3196.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.collective-evolution.com/2015/12/29/report-heres-how-many-people-fatally-overdosed-on-marijuana-in-2015/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7378207a-685f-4977-87a4-9a4909d42474</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 06:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[6 Great Reasons To Give Up Alcohol]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>6 Great Reasons To Give Up Alcohol</h1><p>There's something trending right now and, for once, it may actually be a bandwagon worth jumping on. January is shaping up to be a dry-out month, meaning people have committed to not drinking for the next 31 days. Maybe it's because people overindulged over the holidays, enjoying one (or two, or three) drinks too many [...]</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/974d004d56bf8ebabe4adfedd621310bad933433.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.collective-evolution.com/2016/01/10/6-great-reasons-to-give-up-alcohol/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9288fd2c-3851-4e2b-b033-ede08cc725f1</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 06:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The 3 deadliest drugs in America are all totally legal]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The 3 deadliest drugs in America are all totally legal</h1><p>As the US debates drug policy reforms and marijuana legalization, there's one aspect of the war on drugs that remains perplexingly contradictory: Some of the most dangerous drugs in the US are legal. Don't believe it?</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/89bd793525f15029d5c1f7d3882195293b0499c5.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.vox.com/2014/5/19/5727712/the-three-deadliest-drugs-in-america-are-all-totally-legal</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f0ab5c3a-273c-4752-9df7-c2ab22abe8fe</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 06:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[More Americans died of drug overdoses in 2014 than any other year on record. Here's why.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>More Americans died of drug overdoses in 2014 than any other year on record. Here's why.</h1><p>In 2014, more Americans died of drug overdoses than any other year on record: more than 47,000 deaths in just one year, according to new federal data. That's far more than the nearly 34,000 who died to car crashes, the almost 34,000 who died to gun violence, and the nearly 42,000 who died to HIV/AIDS during that epidemic's peak in 1995.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/77dc4198476cf0d5b5c6b5ca82129ecf4d653aed.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.vox.com/2015/10/1/9433099/opioid-painkiller-heroin-epidemic</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">569e9ffc-b1fe-4e6b-9888-c1a2cef39043</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 06:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[24 maps and charts that explain marijuana]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>24 maps and charts that explain marijuana</h1><p>People have been growing and using marijuana for thousands of years. Ancient texts praised the plant for its versatility - it was used for its psychoactive and medical effects and to make clothes and paper. But in 1934, the US effectively banned the plant with strict taxes and regulations - a prohibition that, despite some major changes to the regulatory model, remains to this day.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/64afa65141c1bb371071a3e54f673dae6ad88983.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.vox.com/2014/10/1/6872975/marijuana-legalization-maps-charts-facts</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">783e6ccf-b671-428e-9b2c-2ee5dfbb3681</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 06:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The risks of alcohol, marijuana, and other drugs, explained]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The risks of alcohol, marijuana, and other drugs, explained</h1><p>Researchers have said for years that alcohol is more dangerous than marijuana. But what does that mean, exactly? And how do we know? It's certainly not because of any government-acknowledged evaluation. The federal government's scheduling system evaluates drugs by medical value, first, and abuse potential, which is poorly defined under the law, second - but it excludes alcohol and tobacco altogether.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/89bd793525f15029d5c1f7d3882195293b0499c5.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.vox.com/2015/2/25/8104917/drug-dangers-marijuana-alcohol</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">64d6f834-a292-478f-8270-776f8f6dbcb0</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 06:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How scientists rank drugs from most to least dangerous - and why the rankings are flawed]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>How scientists rank drugs from most to least dangerous - and why the rankings are flawed</h1><p>There's a very common drug-policy talking point that's meant to convey the absurdity of the war on drugs: Alcohol is more dangerous than marijuana, even though alcohol is legal and marijuana is not. Perhaps the biggest supporting evidence for this point is a 2010 study published in The Lancet that ranked alcohol as the most dangerous drug in the United Kingdom, surpassing heroin, crack cocaine, and marijuana.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/b2cb7334b203723f1cfe84cb69d7ad21f8941051.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.vox.com/2015/2/24/8094759/alcohol-marijuana</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0a189aec-40b2-49f3-bbec-83b14a8b049d</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 06:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No, marijuana isn't a gateway drug]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>No, marijuana isn't a gateway drug</h1><p>There's more evidence that marijuana does not, in fact, lead to harder drug use. marijuana use might not be as dangerous as some critics of the drug fear A new study from Emory University researchers looked at federal surveys and states that legalized medical marijuana to evaluate the impact of legalization on marijuana and other drug use.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/c2998650b5943927b707304c7c81a133ea52be66.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.vox.com/2014/5/15/5717074/no-marijuana-isnt-a-gateway-drug</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">430ea065-09f6-401d-923e-f72d74389826</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 06:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[I'm a doctor. I worry every time I prescribe painkillers to a patient.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>I'm a doctor. I worry every time I prescribe painkillers to a patient.</h1><p>"Please, I need my Oxycodone!" my patient, M, pleaded with me. My eyes met his. I observed every fleeting facial expression, hoping to gauge his intentions. The discussion about whether to continue to prescribe this medication was one I'd had too many times with too many patients over the past few months.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/5ee54b25a83dcf8030eec4b5a67b702ca490aef4.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.vox.com/2016/1/14/10760992/painkiller-prescription</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8dfd742c-bc94-48be-acbb-2d220ea7f8f3</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 02:55:23 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Watch: A neuroscientist debunks common beliefs about drug addiction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Watch: A neuroscientist debunks common beliefs about drug addiction</h1><p>Carl Hart is a neuroscientist and drug addiction expert at Columbia University. In a recent TEDMED talk, Hart spoke about drug addiction and the many misconceptions surrounding the topic - and how those misconceptions can mislead drug policy. Hart went into neuroscience to cure the drug addiction he blamed for causing crime and poverty in his old Miami neighborhood.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/47559ed6d18c394a5a761ae9bb8216b2a83f4188.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.vox.com/2014/9/18/6375039/a-neuroscientist-debunks-common-beliefs-about-drug-addiction</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">fb2b82ec-0394-4ded-a771-050efce006da</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 02:54:32 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>